{"created_at": "2026-04-14T19:14:32.851046+00:00", "text": "my name is Ankit I live I Jaipur and worked in Mumbai", "entities": [[11, 16, "PERSON"], [26, 32, "GPE"], [47, 53, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-14T21:12:24.855681+00:00", "text": "I am Niket Kumar, and I live in California, work at Google", "entities": [[5, 16, "PERSON"], [32, 42, "GPE"], [52, 58, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-14T21:12:52.707482+00:00", "text": "I am Niket Kumar, and I live in California, work at Microsoft", "entities": [[5, 16, "PERSON"], [32, 42, "GPE"], [52, 61, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-20T22:16:01.917158+00:00", "text": "Sundar Pichai announced in California that Google will invest $2 billion in AI research across Europe, India, and Japan by 2027. The initiative, led by Priya Sharma from IIT Bombay, was unveiled at the annual summit on 15 March.", "entities": [[0, 13, "PERSON"], [27, 37, "GPE"], [43, 49, "ORG"], [62, 72, "MONEY"], [95, 101, "GPE"], [103, 108, "GPE"], [114, 119, "GPE"], [123, 127, "DATE"], [152, 164, "PERSON"], [170, 180, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-20T22:16:38.620036+00:00", "text": "Priya sharma lives in California.", "entities": [[0, 5, "PERSON"], [22, 32, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-20T22:16:50.905409+00:00", "text": "Priya sharma lives in California.", "entities": [[0, 5, "PERSON"], [22, 32, "GPE"]]}
