{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772293+00:00", "text": "Flipkart reported a revenue increase of 12% in January 2023.", "entities": [[0, 8, "ORG"], [40, 43, "PERCENT"], [47, 59, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772507+00:00", "text": "World Bank raised 50 million euros in its Series B round on last Monday.", "entities": [[0, 10, "ORG"], [18, 34, "MONEY"], [60, 71, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772517+00:00", "text": "My name is Deepa Iyer and I work at ICICI Bank in New York.", "entities": [[11, 21, "PERSON"], [36, 46, "ORG"], [50, 58, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772523+00:00", "text": "The headquarters of ICICI Bank is located in Canada.", "entities": [[20, 30, "ORG"], [45, 51, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772529+00:00", "text": "The deal worth ₹10 lakh was signed in Q3 2025.", "entities": [[15, 23, "MONEY"], [38, 45, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772534+00:00", "text": "James Rao is the CEO of Ola.", "entities": [[0, 9, "PERSON"], [24, 27, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772538+00:00", "text": "Uber announced on March 2025 that it will expand operations in Vadodara.", "entities": [[0, 4, "ORG"], [18, 28, "DATE"], [63, 71, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772543+00:00", "text": "IIT Delhi plans to invest ₹2,000 in Tokyo by this year.", "entities": [[0, 9, "ORG"], [26, 32, "MONEY"], [45, 54, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772548+00:00", "text": "The deal worth ₹50 crore was signed in two years ago.", "entities": [[15, 24, "MONEY"], [39, 52, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772552+00:00", "text": "Revenue grew by nearly 80% to 50 million euros in Q3 2025.", "entities": [[16, 26, "PERCENT"], [30, 46, "MONEY"], [50, 57, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772556+00:00", "text": "Wipro reported a revenue increase of up by 15% in in 2022.", "entities": [[0, 5, "ORG"], [37, 46, "PERCENT"], [50, 57, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772560+00:00", "text": "Revenue grew by over 30% to $500 million in 3rd April 2024.", "entities": [[16, 24, "PERCENT"], [28, 40, "MONEY"], [44, 58, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772565+00:00", "text": "Byju's announced on January 2023 that it will expand operations in Chennai.", "entities": [[0, 6, "ORG"], [20, 32, "DATE"], [67, 74, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772569+00:00", "text": "Meta plans to invest $500 million in France by the 1990s.", "entities": [[0, 4, "ORG"], [21, 33, "MONEY"], [47, 56, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772573+00:00", "text": "According to Sophia Verma, the office in France will be expanded.", "entities": [[13, 25, "PERSON"], [41, 47, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772578+00:00", "text": "Charlie Singh was born in Patna and studied at Infosys.", "entities": [[0, 13, "PERSON"], [26, 31, "GPE"], [47, 54, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772582+00:00", "text": "Revenue grew by a 7% drop to $500 million in 3rd April 2024.", "entities": [[16, 25, "PERCENT"], [29, 41, "MONEY"], [45, 59, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772586+00:00", "text": "Alice Johnson moved from Ahmedabad to pursue a career at Apple.", "entities": [[0, 13, "PERSON"], [25, 34, "GPE"], [57, 62, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772590+00:00", "text": "United Nations partnered with another firm based in Hyderabad on on 15 August.", "entities": [[0, 14, "ORG"], [52, 61, "GPE"], [65, 77, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772594+00:00", "text": "DRDO announced on this year that it will expand operations in Vadodara.", "entities": [[0, 4, "ORG"], [18, 27, "DATE"], [62, 70, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772598+00:00", "text": "Revenue grew by just 2% to ₹2,000 in Q3 2025.", "entities": [[16, 23, "PERCENT"], [27, 33, "MONEY"], [37, 44, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772602+00:00", "text": "Arjun Jain moved from Vadodara to pursue a career at Google.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [22, 30, "GPE"], [53, 59, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772605+00:00", "text": "Paytm reported a revenue increase of 4.5% in the 1990s.", "entities": [[0, 5, "ORG"], [37, 41, "PERCENT"], [45, 54, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772610+00:00", "text": "My name is Amit Jain and I work at Wipro in Tokyo.", "entities": [[11, 20, "PERSON"], [35, 40, "ORG"], [44, 49, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772613+00:00", "text": "The headquarters of Microsoft is located in Ahmedabad.", "entities": [[20, 29, "ORG"], [44, 53, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772616+00:00", "text": "Liam Sinha is the CEO of State Bank of India.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [25, 44, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772620+00:00", "text": "Tanya Bose moved from Hyderabad to pursue a career at Oxford University.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [22, 31, "GPE"], [54, 71, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772624+00:00", "text": "Divya White moved from Paris to pursue a career at Stanford University.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [23, 28, "GPE"], [51, 70, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772628+00:00", "text": "I am Charlie Trivedi and I live in Australia.", "entities": [[5, 20, "PERSON"], [35, 44, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772635+00:00", "text": "The majority of Americans in Kochi speak English as their first language.", "entities": [[16, 25, "NORP"], [29, 34, "GPE"], [41, 48, "LANGUAGE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772640+00:00", "text": "I am Niket Patel and I live in Bhopal.", "entities": [[5, 16, "PERSON"], [31, 37, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772643+00:00", "text": "Karan Martin is the CEO of Apple.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [27, 32, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772650+00:00", "text": "Shruti Mehta from Ola will speak at the conference in Hyderabad on this year around midnight.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [18, 21, "ORG"], [54, 63, "GPE"], [67, 76, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772655+00:00", "text": "Stanford University announced on January 2023 that it will expand operations in Japan.", "entities": [[0, 19, "ORG"], [33, 45, "DATE"], [80, 85, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772658+00:00", "text": "Niket Verma left University of California in United States after five years.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [17, 41, "ORG"], [45, 58, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772662+00:00", "text": "The headquarters of Tesla is located in Chennai.", "entities": [[20, 25, "ORG"], [40, 47, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772666+00:00", "text": "Revenue grew by nearly 80% to $500 million in this year.", "entities": [[16, 26, "PERCENT"], [30, 42, "MONEY"], [46, 55, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772669+00:00", "text": "According to Priya Dubey, the office in Coimbatore will be expanded.", "entities": [[13, 24, "PERSON"], [40, 50, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772673+00:00", "text": "Kavya Dubey is the CEO of Meta.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [26, 30, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772676+00:00", "text": "Pooja Gupta is the CEO of NASSCOM.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [26, 33, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772682+00:00", "text": "State Bank of India introduced ChatGPT on on 15 August at a price of $1.2 billion.", "entities": [[0, 19, "ORG"], [31, 38, "PRODUCT"], [42, 54, "DATE"], [69, 81, "MONEY"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772686+00:00", "text": "According to Isha Kumar, the office in Vadodara will be expanded.", "entities": [[13, 23, "PERSON"], [39, 47, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772690+00:00", "text": "Sophia Taylor moved from London to pursue a career at Securities Exchange Board of India.", "entities": [[0, 13, "PERSON"], [25, 31, "GPE"], [54, 88, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772694+00:00", "text": "My name is Rohit Smith and I work at HDFC Bank in Chennai.", "entities": [[11, 22, "PERSON"], [37, 46, "ORG"], [50, 57, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772698+00:00", "text": "The deal worth $1.2 billion was signed in this year.", "entities": [[15, 27, "MONEY"], [42, 51, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772701+00:00", "text": "Srishti Singh moved from Kolkata to pursue a career at ISRO.", "entities": [[0, 13, "PERSON"], [25, 32, "GPE"], [55, 59, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772705+00:00", "text": "Niket Yadav left Meta in Patna after five years.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [17, 21, "ORG"], [25, 30, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772709+00:00", "text": "My name is James Jain and I work at Reserve Bank of India in Patna.", "entities": [[11, 21, "PERSON"], [36, 57, "ORG"], [61, 66, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772712+00:00", "text": "The headquarters of World Bank is located in Berlin.", "entities": [[20, 30, "ORG"], [45, 51, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772718+00:00", "text": "Meera Moore presented the product Pixel 8 at 10:30 AM at HDFC Bank in India.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [34, 41, "PRODUCT"], [57, 66, "ORG"], [70, 75, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772721+00:00", "text": "Alice Brown is the CEO of WHO.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [26, 29, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772725+00:00", "text": "Shruti Taylor was born in New York and studied at HDFC Bank.", "entities": [[0, 13, "PERSON"], [26, 34, "GPE"], [50, 59, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772728+00:00", "text": "I am David Joshi and I live in Hyderabad.", "entities": [[5, 16, "PERSON"], [31, 40, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772732+00:00", "text": "The headquarters of Harvard University is located in Tokyo.", "entities": [[20, 38, "ORG"], [53, 58, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772736+00:00", "text": "Securities Exchange Board of India announced on two years ago that it will expand operations in Kochi.", "entities": [[0, 34, "ORG"], [48, 61, "DATE"], [96, 101, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772741+00:00", "text": "The majority of Asians in Vadodara speak Kannada as their first language.", "entities": [[16, 22, "NORP"], [26, 34, "GPE"], [41, 48, "LANGUAGE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772745+00:00", "text": "According to Sanjay Gupta, the office in New York will be expanded.", "entities": [[13, 25, "PERSON"], [41, 49, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772749+00:00", "text": "Neha Tiwari left Apple in Kolkata after five years.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [17, 22, "ORG"], [26, 33, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772753+00:00", "text": "Ola plans to invest 1 million dollars in Bangalore by two years ago.", "entities": [[0, 3, "ORG"], [20, 37, "MONEY"], [54, 67, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772756+00:00", "text": "Zoe Kapoor left Harvard University in Paris after five years.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [16, 34, "ORG"], [38, 43, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772760+00:00", "text": "Meta announced on this year that it will expand operations in Surat.", "entities": [[0, 4, "ORG"], [18, 27, "DATE"], [62, 67, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772764+00:00", "text": "University of California plans to invest 1 million dollars in Sydney by last Monday.", "entities": [[0, 24, "ORG"], [41, 58, "MONEY"], [72, 83, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772768+00:00", "text": "Uber reported a revenue increase of 12% in two years ago.", "entities": [[0, 4, "ORG"], [36, 39, "PERCENT"], [43, 56, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772771+00:00", "text": "The deal worth 1 million dollars was signed in January 2023.", "entities": [[15, 32, "MONEY"], [47, 59, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772777+00:00", "text": "David Joshi presented the product Surface Pro at noon at HCL Technologies in Japan.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [34, 45, "PRODUCT"], [57, 73, "ORG"], [77, 82, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772781+00:00", "text": "Stanford University partnered with another firm based in Bhopal on January 2023.", "entities": [[0, 19, "ORG"], [57, 63, "GPE"], [67, 79, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772785+00:00", "text": "My name is Kunal Thomas and I work at ICICI Bank in Bhopal.", "entities": [[11, 23, "PERSON"], [38, 48, "ORG"], [52, 58, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772789+00:00", "text": "Flipkart plans to invest ₹2,000 in France by March 2025.", "entities": [[0, 8, "ORG"], [25, 31, "MONEY"], [45, 55, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772793+00:00", "text": "NASSCOM announced on last Monday that it will expand operations in China.", "entities": [[0, 7, "ORG"], [21, 32, "DATE"], [67, 72, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772798+00:00", "text": "The majority of Republicans in Kanpur speak Malayalam as their first language.", "entities": [[16, 27, "NORP"], [31, 37, "GPE"], [44, 53, "LANGUAGE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772802+00:00", "text": "The headquarters of IIT Delhi is located in Berlin.", "entities": [[20, 29, "ORG"], [44, 50, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772805+00:00", "text": "I am William Sinha and I live in Mumbai.", "entities": [[5, 18, "PERSON"], [33, 39, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772809+00:00", "text": "Ola announced on two years ago that it will expand operations in India.", "entities": [[0, 3, "ORG"], [17, 30, "DATE"], [65, 70, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772813+00:00", "text": "IISc Bangalore plans to invest ₹10 lakh in Kochi by on 15 August.", "entities": [[0, 14, "ORG"], [31, 39, "MONEY"], [52, 64, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772817+00:00", "text": "IISc Bangalore reported a revenue increase of nearly 80% in two years ago.", "entities": [[0, 14, "ORG"], [46, 56, "PERCENT"], [60, 73, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772820+00:00", "text": "The headquarters of IIT Bombay is located in Paris.", "entities": [[20, 30, "ORG"], [45, 50, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772823+00:00", "text": "The report by Ravi Mehta from University of California shows impressive growth.", "entities": [[14, 24, "PERSON"], [30, 54, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772828+00:00", "text": "HDFC Bank reported a revenue increase of more than 50% in by December.", "entities": [[0, 9, "ORG"], [41, 54, "PERCENT"], [58, 69, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772832+00:00", "text": "Netflix plans to invest $500 million in Visakhapatnam by two years ago.", "entities": [[0, 7, "ORG"], [24, 36, "MONEY"], [57, 70, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772836+00:00", "text": "My name is Liam Agarwal and I work at Reliance Industries in Surat.", "entities": [[11, 23, "PERSON"], [38, 57, "ORG"], [61, 66, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772839+00:00", "text": "According to Noah Sharma, the office in Hyderabad will be expanded.", "entities": [[13, 24, "PERSON"], [40, 49, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772843+00:00", "text": "IIT Delhi reported a revenue increase of nearly 80% in on 15 August.", "entities": [[0, 9, "ORG"], [41, 51, "PERCENT"], [55, 67, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772847+00:00", "text": "Sneha Sharma left Google in Pune after five years.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [18, 24, "ORG"], [28, 32, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772851+00:00", "text": "My name is Gaurav Taylor and I work at DRDO in Singapore.", "entities": [[11, 24, "PERSON"], [39, 43, "ORG"], [47, 56, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772854+00:00", "text": "MIT partnered with another firm based in Jaipur on March 2025.", "entities": [[0, 3, "ORG"], [41, 47, "GPE"], [51, 61, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772858+00:00", "text": "Revenue grew by up by 15% to ₹3.5 crore in on 15 August.", "entities": [[16, 25, "PERCENT"], [29, 39, "MONEY"], [43, 55, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772864+00:00", "text": "Vikram Verma presented the product Surface Pro around midnight at Stanford University in Canada.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [35, 46, "PRODUCT"], [66, 85, "ORG"], [89, 95, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772868+00:00", "text": "Ola raised ₹10 lakh in its Series B round on this year.", "entities": [[0, 3, "ORG"], [11, 19, "MONEY"], [45, 54, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772872+00:00", "text": "Divya Verma moved from Germany to pursue a career at ICICI Bank.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [23, 30, "GPE"], [53, 63, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772875+00:00", "text": "Revenue grew by a 7% drop to ₹10 lakh in this year.", "entities": [[16, 25, "PERCENT"], [29, 37, "MONEY"], [41, 50, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772879+00:00", "text": "Investors in Germany welcomed IISc Bangalore's strategic announcement.", "entities": [[13, 20, "GPE"], [30, 44, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772884+00:00", "text": "Srishti Verma from Microsoft will speak at the conference in Berlin on on 15 August in the afternoon.", "entities": [[0, 13, "PERSON"], [19, 28, "ORG"], [61, 67, "GPE"], [71, 83, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772888+00:00", "text": "Revenue grew by more than 50% to €200 billion in on 15 August.", "entities": [[16, 29, "PERCENT"], [33, 45, "MONEY"], [49, 61, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772892+00:00", "text": "Shruti Kumar moved from France to pursue a career at Ola.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [24, 30, "GPE"], [53, 56, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772896+00:00", "text": "Revenue grew by 12% to ₹50 crore in next Friday.", "entities": [[16, 19, "PERCENT"], [23, 32, "MONEY"], [36, 47, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772900+00:00", "text": "My name is Maria Taylor and I work at MIT in Kanpur.", "entities": [[11, 23, "PERSON"], [38, 41, "ORG"], [45, 51, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772909+00:00", "text": "According to Sakshi Gupta, the office in Indore will be expanded.", "entities": [[13, 25, "PERSON"], [41, 47, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772913+00:00", "text": "Karan Dubey left IIT Delhi in Coimbatore after five years.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [17, 26, "ORG"], [30, 40, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772917+00:00", "text": "My name is Kunal Davis and I work at Netflix in Dubai.", "entities": [[11, 22, "PERSON"], [37, 44, "ORG"], [48, 53, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772921+00:00", "text": "ICICI Bank raised ₹2,000 in its Series B round on March 2025.", "entities": [[0, 10, "ORG"], [18, 24, "MONEY"], [50, 60, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772943+00:00", "text": "The headquarters of Reserve Bank of India is located in Indore.", "entities": [[20, 41, "ORG"], [56, 62, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772947+00:00", "text": "Wipro raised €200 billion in its Series B round on next Friday.", "entities": [[0, 5, "ORG"], [13, 25, "MONEY"], [51, 62, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772954+00:00", "text": "Grace Moore from Reserve Bank of India will speak at the conference in Germany on on 15 August around midnight.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [17, 38, "ORG"], [71, 78, "GPE"], [82, 94, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772958+00:00", "text": "Swiggy plans to invest ₹2,000 in United States by this year.", "entities": [[0, 6, "ORG"], [23, 29, "MONEY"], [50, 59, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772961+00:00", "text": "Divya Pillai is the CEO of IISc Bangalore.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [27, 41, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772965+00:00", "text": "MIT reported a revenue increase of up by 15% in on 15 August.", "entities": [[0, 3, "ORG"], [35, 44, "PERCENT"], [48, 60, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772969+00:00", "text": "MIT plans to invest 50 million euros in Coimbatore by early 2026.", "entities": [[0, 3, "ORG"], [20, 36, "MONEY"], [54, 64, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772973+00:00", "text": "Akash Chaudhary was born in Kolkata and studied at State Bank of India.", "entities": [[0, 15, "PERSON"], [28, 35, "GPE"], [51, 70, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772980+00:00", "text": "Tanya Singh authored Inception, which sold over 12% more copies in Singapore.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [21, 30, "WORK_OF_ART"], [48, 51, "PERCENT"], [67, 76, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772984+00:00", "text": "The headquarters of Ola is located in Coimbatore.", "entities": [[20, 23, "ORG"], [38, 48, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772987+00:00", "text": "Netflix partnered with another firm based in Patna on early 2026.", "entities": [[0, 7, "ORG"], [45, 50, "GPE"], [54, 64, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772991+00:00", "text": "Stanford University announced on by December that it will expand operations in London.", "entities": [[0, 19, "ORG"], [33, 44, "DATE"], [79, 85, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772994+00:00", "text": "I am Manish Pillai and I live in France.", "entities": [[5, 18, "PERSON"], [33, 39, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.772998+00:00", "text": "According to Rahul Pillai, the office in United Kingdom will be expanded.", "entities": [[13, 25, "PERSON"], [41, 55, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773001+00:00", "text": "The headquarters of University of California is located in Paris.", "entities": [[20, 44, "ORG"], [59, 64, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773004+00:00", "text": "The deal worth $500 million was signed in next Friday.", "entities": [[15, 27, "MONEY"], [42, 53, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773008+00:00", "text": "I am Vikram Thomas and I live in Kanpur.", "entities": [[5, 18, "PERSON"], [33, 39, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773012+00:00", "text": "Olivia Yadav was born in Coimbatore and studied at Stanford University.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [25, 35, "GPE"], [51, 70, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773017+00:00", "text": "Pooja Smith presented the product Copilot before 6 PM at Reliance Industries in Visakhapatnam.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [34, 41, "PRODUCT"], [57, 76, "ORG"], [80, 93, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773023+00:00", "text": "Securities Exchange Board of India introduced iPhone 15 on early 2026 at a price of $1.2 billion.", "entities": [[0, 34, "ORG"], [46, 55, "PRODUCT"], [59, 69, "DATE"], [84, 96, "MONEY"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773027+00:00", "text": "HCL Technologies partnered with another firm based in Chennai on Q3 2025.", "entities": [[0, 16, "ORG"], [54, 61, "GPE"], [65, 72, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773030+00:00", "text": "According to Amit Taylor, the office in France will be expanded.", "entities": [[13, 24, "PERSON"], [40, 46, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773034+00:00", "text": "Aditya Kapoor moved from Surat to pursue a career at Apple.", "entities": [[0, 13, "PERSON"], [25, 30, "GPE"], [53, 58, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773037+00:00", "text": "Revenue grew by 4.5% to ₹2,000 in this year.", "entities": [[16, 20, "PERCENT"], [24, 30, "MONEY"], [34, 43, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773041+00:00", "text": "DRDO partnered with another firm based in Germany on by December.", "entities": [[0, 4, "ORG"], [42, 49, "GPE"], [53, 64, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773044+00:00", "text": "Yash Kapoor was born in Australia and studied at World Bank.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [24, 33, "GPE"], [49, 59, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773049+00:00", "text": "WHO reported a revenue increase of 12% in March 2025.", "entities": [[0, 3, "ORG"], [35, 38, "PERCENT"], [42, 52, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773053+00:00", "text": "Netflix reported a revenue increase of just 2% in January 2023.", "entities": [[0, 7, "ORG"], [39, 46, "PERCENT"], [50, 62, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773056+00:00", "text": "Investors in Japan welcomed Google's strategic announcement.", "entities": [[13, 18, "GPE"], [28, 34, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773059+00:00", "text": "The headquarters of ICICI Bank is located in Visakhapatnam.", "entities": [[20, 30, "ORG"], [45, 58, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773063+00:00", "text": "The deal worth €200 billion was signed in March 2025.", "entities": [[15, 27, "MONEY"], [42, 52, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773066+00:00", "text": "TCS announced on 3rd April 2024 that it will expand operations in Coimbatore.", "entities": [[0, 3, "ORG"], [17, 31, "DATE"], [66, 76, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773070+00:00", "text": "Aarav Mehta was born in Berlin and studied at Paytm.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [24, 30, "GPE"], [46, 51, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773073+00:00", "text": "Investors in France welcomed Paytm's strategic announcement.", "entities": [[13, 19, "GPE"], [29, 34, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773076+00:00", "text": "The headquarters of Netflix is located in Bangalore.", "entities": [[20, 27, "ORG"], [42, 51, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773080+00:00", "text": "Investors in Bhopal welcomed Netflix's strategic announcement.", "entities": [[13, 19, "GPE"], [29, 36, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773083+00:00", "text": "Flipkart reported a revenue increase of 12% in last Monday.", "entities": [[0, 8, "ORG"], [40, 43, "PERCENT"], [47, 58, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773087+00:00", "text": "Flipkart partnered with another firm based in Kanpur on the 1990s.", "entities": [[0, 8, "ORG"], [46, 52, "GPE"], [56, 65, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773090+00:00", "text": "Netflix partnered with another firm based in Dubai on in 2022.", "entities": [[0, 7, "ORG"], [45, 50, "GPE"], [54, 61, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773093+00:00", "text": "The report by Arjun Bansal from Tesla shows impressive growth.", "entities": [[14, 26, "PERSON"], [32, 37, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773099+00:00", "text": "Investors in France welcomed Zomato's strategic announcement.", "entities": [[13, 19, "GPE"], [29, 35, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773104+00:00", "text": "Akash Thomas was born in India and studied at Netflix.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [25, 30, "GPE"], [46, 53, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773108+00:00", "text": "My name is Emma Wilson and I work at IIT Bombay in New York.", "entities": [[11, 22, "PERSON"], [37, 47, "ORG"], [51, 59, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773111+00:00", "text": "IISc Bangalore plans to invest ₹50 crore in Tokyo by January 2023.", "entities": [[0, 14, "ORG"], [31, 40, "MONEY"], [53, 65, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773115+00:00", "text": "The headquarters of Harvard University is located in Chennai.", "entities": [[20, 38, "ORG"], [53, 60, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773118+00:00", "text": "Harvard University announced on next Friday that it will expand operations in London.", "entities": [[0, 18, "ORG"], [32, 43, "DATE"], [78, 84, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773124+00:00", "text": "Deepa Verma presented the product ChatGPT at noon at United Nations in Patna.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [34, 41, "PRODUCT"], [53, 67, "ORG"], [71, 76, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773129+00:00", "text": "The headquarters of TCS is located in London.", "entities": [[20, 23, "ORG"], [38, 44, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773133+00:00", "text": "IISc Bangalore reported a revenue increase of just 2% in by December.", "entities": [[0, 14, "ORG"], [46, 53, "PERCENT"], [57, 68, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773141+00:00", "text": "Investors in Nagpur welcomed IIT Delhi's strategic announcement.", "entities": [[13, 19, "GPE"], [29, 38, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773145+00:00", "text": "Flipkart plans to invest 50 million euros in Jaipur by in 2022.", "entities": [[0, 8, "ORG"], [25, 41, "MONEY"], [55, 62, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773149+00:00", "text": "Revenue grew by just 2% to $1.2 billion in 3rd April 2024.", "entities": [[16, 23, "PERCENT"], [27, 39, "MONEY"], [43, 57, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773152+00:00", "text": "Investors in Paris welcomed Ola's strategic announcement.", "entities": [[13, 18, "GPE"], [28, 31, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773155+00:00", "text": "Reliance Industries partnered with another firm based in Patna on the 1990s.", "entities": [[0, 19, "ORG"], [57, 62, "GPE"], [66, 75, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773159+00:00", "text": "The report by Meera Iyer from IISc Bangalore shows impressive growth.", "entities": [[14, 24, "PERSON"], [30, 44, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773163+00:00", "text": "The deal worth $1.2 billion was signed in last Monday.", "entities": [[15, 27, "MONEY"], [42, 53, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773166+00:00", "text": "Investors in Canada welcomed Tesla's strategic announcement.", "entities": [[13, 19, "GPE"], [29, 34, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773172+00:00", "text": "Google introduced Pixel 8 on on 15 August at a price of ₹2,000.", "entities": [[0, 6, "ORG"], [18, 25, "PRODUCT"], [29, 41, "DATE"], [56, 62, "MONEY"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773176+00:00", "text": "NASSCOM partnered with another firm based in Germany on in 2022.", "entities": [[0, 7, "ORG"], [45, 52, "GPE"], [56, 63, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773182+00:00", "text": "Amit Nair authored The Alchemist, which sold over 4.5% more copies in Hyderabad.", "entities": [[0, 9, "PERSON"], [19, 32, "WORK_OF_ART"], [50, 54, "PERCENT"], [70, 79, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773186+00:00", "text": "Byju's plans to invest ₹50 crore in Delhi by Q3 2025.", "entities": [[0, 6, "ORG"], [23, 32, "MONEY"], [45, 52, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773189+00:00", "text": "Investors in San Francisco welcomed State Bank of India's strategic announcement.", "entities": [[13, 26, "GPE"], [36, 55, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773193+00:00", "text": "Revenue grew by over 30% to ₹2,000 in the 1990s.", "entities": [[16, 24, "PERCENT"], [28, 34, "MONEY"], [38, 47, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773196+00:00", "text": "Oxford University reported a revenue increase of nearly 80% in 3rd April 2024.", "entities": [[0, 17, "ORG"], [49, 59, "PERCENT"], [63, 77, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773200+00:00", "text": "MIT announced on two years ago that it will expand operations in Vadodara.", "entities": [[0, 3, "ORG"], [17, 30, "DATE"], [65, 73, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773205+00:00", "text": "MIT introduced Google Maps on two years ago at a price of ₹2,000.", "entities": [[0, 3, "ORG"], [15, 26, "PRODUCT"], [30, 43, "DATE"], [58, 64, "MONEY"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773209+00:00", "text": "Reliance Industries raised 50 million euros in its Series B round on by December.", "entities": [[0, 19, "ORG"], [27, 43, "MONEY"], [69, 80, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773213+00:00", "text": "Noah Singh was born in United States and studied at Reserve Bank of India.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [23, 36, "GPE"], [52, 73, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773218+00:00", "text": "Zomato introduced iPhone 15 on two years ago at a price of €200 billion.", "entities": [[0, 6, "ORG"], [18, 27, "PRODUCT"], [31, 44, "DATE"], [59, 71, "MONEY"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773222+00:00", "text": "The deal worth ₹10 lakh was signed in January 2023.", "entities": [[15, 23, "MONEY"], [38, 50, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773226+00:00", "text": "Tesla partnered with another firm based in Bangalore on Q3 2025.", "entities": [[0, 5, "ORG"], [43, 52, "GPE"], [56, 63, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773230+00:00", "text": "Emma Gupta is the CEO of Swiggy.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [25, 31, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773235+00:00", "text": "The majority of Europeans in Japan speak Punjabi as their first language.", "entities": [[16, 25, "NORP"], [29, 34, "GPE"], [41, 48, "LANGUAGE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773242+00:00", "text": "Stanford University introduced MacBook Pro on early 2026 at a price of ₹2,000.", "entities": [[0, 19, "ORG"], [31, 42, "PRODUCT"], [46, 56, "DATE"], [71, 77, "MONEY"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773247+00:00", "text": "The majority of Hindus in United Kingdom speak Punjabi as their first language.", "entities": [[16, 22, "NORP"], [26, 40, "GPE"], [47, 54, "LANGUAGE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773251+00:00", "text": "Tesla announced on by December that it will expand operations in Bhopal.", "entities": [[0, 5, "ORG"], [19, 30, "DATE"], [65, 71, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773255+00:00", "text": "WHO announced on two years ago that it will expand operations in Bhopal.", "entities": [[0, 3, "ORG"], [17, 30, "DATE"], [65, 71, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773258+00:00", "text": "Paytm reported a revenue increase of more than 50% in next Friday.", "entities": [[0, 5, "ORG"], [37, 50, "PERCENT"], [54, 65, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773262+00:00", "text": "According to Niket Iyer, the office in Kochi will be expanded.", "entities": [[13, 23, "PERSON"], [39, 44, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773265+00:00", "text": "Emma Sinha moved from Tokyo to pursue a career at State Bank of India.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [22, 27, "GPE"], [50, 69, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773269+00:00", "text": "NASSCOM reported a revenue increase of up by 15% in the 1990s.", "entities": [[0, 7, "ORG"], [39, 48, "PERCENT"], [52, 61, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773275+00:00", "text": "Tesla introduced OnePlus 12 on the 1990s at a price of €200 billion.", "entities": [[0, 5, "ORG"], [17, 27, "PRODUCT"], [31, 40, "DATE"], [55, 67, "MONEY"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773281+00:00", "text": "Kavya Lee presented the product ChatGPT before 6 PM at Swiggy in Pune.", "entities": [[0, 9, "PERSON"], [32, 39, "PRODUCT"], [55, 61, "ORG"], [65, 69, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773287+00:00", "text": "Vikas Kapoor from MIT will speak at the conference in Kolkata on two years ago around midnight.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [18, 21, "ORG"], [54, 61, "GPE"], [65, 78, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773290+00:00", "text": "I am Liam Thomas and I live in Indore.", "entities": [[5, 16, "PERSON"], [31, 37, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773294+00:00", "text": "The deal worth ₹50 crore was signed in Q3 2025.", "entities": [[15, 24, "MONEY"], [39, 46, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773300+00:00", "text": "Kunal Nair from NASSCOM will speak at the conference in Vadodara on March 2025 at noon.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [16, 23, "ORG"], [56, 64, "GPE"], [68, 78, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773305+00:00", "text": "My name is Aditya Mehta and I work at HCL Technologies in Vadodara.", "entities": [[11, 23, "PERSON"], [38, 54, "ORG"], [58, 66, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773308+00:00", "text": "Vinay Wilson is the CEO of IISc Bangalore.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [27, 41, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773312+00:00", "text": "Swiggy raised ₹3.5 crore in its Series B round on the 1990s.", "entities": [[0, 6, "ORG"], [14, 24, "MONEY"], [50, 59, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773315+00:00", "text": "Investors in Bangalore welcomed WHO's strategic announcement.", "entities": [[13, 22, "GPE"], [32, 35, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773319+00:00", "text": "According to Kunal Lee, the office in Chennai will be expanded.", "entities": [[13, 22, "PERSON"], [38, 45, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773323+00:00", "text": "Oxford University raised $1.2 billion in its Series B round on next Friday.", "entities": [[0, 17, "ORG"], [25, 37, "MONEY"], [63, 74, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773326+00:00", "text": "Arjun Sharma moved from Hyderabad to pursue a career at TCS.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [24, 33, "GPE"], [56, 59, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773333+00:00", "text": "The report by Ethan White from World Bank shows impressive growth.", "entities": [[14, 25, "PERSON"], [31, 41, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773336+00:00", "text": "MIT partnered with another firm based in New York on the 1990s.", "entities": [[0, 3, "ORG"], [41, 49, "GPE"], [53, 62, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773340+00:00", "text": "I am Kunal Jones and I live in Paris.", "entities": [[5, 16, "PERSON"], [31, 36, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773343+00:00", "text": "IISc Bangalore partnered with another firm based in China on by December.", "entities": [[0, 14, "ORG"], [52, 57, "GPE"], [61, 72, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773346+00:00", "text": "The headquarters of Byju's is located in Australia.", "entities": [[20, 26, "ORG"], [41, 50, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773350+00:00", "text": "Stanford University announced on next Friday that it will expand operations in Hyderabad.", "entities": [[0, 19, "ORG"], [33, 44, "DATE"], [79, 88, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773353+00:00", "text": "Rahul Gupta moved from United Kingdom to pursue a career at Tesla.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [23, 37, "GPE"], [60, 65, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773357+00:00", "text": "OpenAI partnered with another firm based in Japan on in 2022.", "entities": [[0, 6, "ORG"], [44, 49, "GPE"], [53, 60, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773363+00:00", "text": "Apple introduced Copilot on the 1990s at a price of ₹10 lakh.", "entities": [[0, 5, "ORG"], [17, 24, "PRODUCT"], [28, 37, "DATE"], [52, 60, "MONEY"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773366+00:00", "text": "The report by James Yadav from Tesla shows impressive growth.", "entities": [[14, 25, "PERSON"], [31, 36, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773370+00:00", "text": "I am Arjun Chaudhary and I live in Berlin.", "entities": [[5, 20, "PERSON"], [35, 41, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773374+00:00", "text": "The deal worth €200 billion was signed in last Monday.", "entities": [[15, 27, "MONEY"], [42, 53, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773377+00:00", "text": "The report by Shruti Mishra from Paytm shows impressive growth.", "entities": [[14, 27, "PERSON"], [33, 38, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773381+00:00", "text": "Akash Reddy left TCS in Berlin after five years.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [17, 20, "ORG"], [24, 30, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773384+00:00", "text": "I am Isha Smith and I live in Kolkata.", "entities": [[5, 15, "PERSON"], [30, 37, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773387+00:00", "text": "The headquarters of Ola is located in Lucknow.", "entities": [[20, 23, "ORG"], [38, 45, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773391+00:00", "text": "Apple raised 1 million dollars in its Series B round on 3rd April 2024.", "entities": [[0, 5, "ORG"], [13, 30, "MONEY"], [56, 70, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773395+00:00", "text": "Revenue grew by more than 50% to $1.2 billion in the 1990s.", "entities": [[16, 29, "PERCENT"], [33, 45, "MONEY"], [49, 58, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773398+00:00", "text": "ISRO partnered with another firm based in Ahmedabad on in 2022.", "entities": [[0, 4, "ORG"], [42, 51, "GPE"], [55, 62, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773402+00:00", "text": "Vikram Moore was born in London and studied at World Bank.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [25, 31, "GPE"], [47, 57, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773409+00:00", "text": "My name is Bob Thomas and I work at IIT Bombay in Chennai.", "entities": [[11, 21, "PERSON"], [36, 46, "ORG"], [50, 57, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773413+00:00", "text": "Nikhil Johnson was born in Jaipur and studied at HDFC Bank.", "entities": [[0, 14, "PERSON"], [27, 33, "GPE"], [49, 58, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773416+00:00", "text": "According to Grace Singh, the office in Mumbai will be expanded.", "entities": [[13, 24, "PERSON"], [40, 46, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773419+00:00", "text": "The deal worth ₹3.5 crore was signed in early 2026.", "entities": [[15, 25, "MONEY"], [40, 50, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773423+00:00", "text": "Meta announced on early 2026 that it will expand operations in France.", "entities": [[0, 4, "ORG"], [18, 28, "DATE"], [63, 69, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773426+00:00", "text": "Meta partnered with another firm based in India on the 1990s.", "entities": [[0, 4, "ORG"], [42, 47, "GPE"], [51, 60, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773430+00:00", "text": "Zomato announced on on 15 August that it will expand operations in Ahmedabad.", "entities": [[0, 6, "ORG"], [20, 32, "DATE"], [67, 76, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773435+00:00", "text": "Amit Martin from Wipro will speak at the conference in Singapore on early 2026 before 6 PM.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [17, 22, "ORG"], [55, 64, "GPE"], [68, 78, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773438+00:00", "text": "The headquarters of IIT Bombay is located in Kochi.", "entities": [[20, 30, "ORG"], [45, 50, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773442+00:00", "text": "Sanjay Garcia is the CEO of Wipro.", "entities": [[0, 13, "PERSON"], [28, 33, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773446+00:00", "text": "Uber reported a revenue increase of nearly 80% in early 2026.", "entities": [[0, 4, "ORG"], [36, 46, "PERCENT"], [50, 60, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773449+00:00", "text": "I am Vikram Davis and I live in Vadodara.", "entities": [[5, 17, "PERSON"], [32, 40, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773452+00:00", "text": "Noah Martinez moved from Hyderabad to pursue a career at TCS.", "entities": [[0, 13, "PERSON"], [25, 34, "GPE"], [57, 60, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773459+00:00", "text": "Oxford University introduced Gemini on March 2025 at a price of ₹10 lakh.", "entities": [[0, 17, "ORG"], [29, 35, "PRODUCT"], [39, 49, "DATE"], [64, 72, "MONEY"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773462+00:00", "text": "Investors in Chennai welcomed World Bank's strategic announcement.", "entities": [[13, 20, "GPE"], [30, 40, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773466+00:00", "text": "My name is Kunal Nair and I work at MIT in Canada.", "entities": [[11, 21, "PERSON"], [36, 39, "ORG"], [43, 49, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773470+00:00", "text": "Ravi Sinha is the CEO of Zomato.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [25, 31, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773473+00:00", "text": "MIT announced on this year that it will expand operations in Sydney.", "entities": [[0, 3, "ORG"], [17, 26, "DATE"], [61, 67, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773478+00:00", "text": "Byju's reported a revenue increase of nearly 80% in this year.", "entities": [[0, 6, "ORG"], [38, 48, "PERCENT"], [52, 61, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773485+00:00", "text": "Gaurav Rao from Harvard University will speak at the conference in Pune on March 2025 before 6 PM.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [16, 34, "ORG"], [67, 71, "GPE"], [75, 85, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773489+00:00", "text": "Swiggy partnered with another firm based in United Kingdom on Q3 2025.", "entities": [[0, 6, "ORG"], [44, 58, "GPE"], [62, 69, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773492+00:00", "text": "The headquarters of United Nations is located in Chennai.", "entities": [[20, 34, "ORG"], [49, 56, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773496+00:00", "text": "Emma Wilson left Tesla in Paris after five years.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [17, 22, "ORG"], [26, 31, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773500+00:00", "text": "The report by Neha Johnson from United Nations shows impressive growth.", "entities": [[14, 26, "PERSON"], [32, 46, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773504+00:00", "text": "Charlie Bansal was born in United States and studied at TCS.", "entities": [[0, 14, "PERSON"], [27, 40, "GPE"], [56, 59, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773510+00:00", "text": "Noah Miller from IIT Bombay will speak at the conference in Jaipur on the 1990s by 5 PM.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [17, 27, "ORG"], [60, 66, "GPE"], [70, 79, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773513+00:00", "text": "The report by Divya Kumar from University of California shows impressive growth.", "entities": [[14, 25, "PERSON"], [31, 55, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773516+00:00", "text": "I am Priya Dubey and I live in Kanpur.", "entities": [[5, 16, "PERSON"], [31, 37, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773520+00:00", "text": "I am Grace Agarwal and I live in Nagpur.", "entities": [[5, 18, "PERSON"], [33, 39, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773525+00:00", "text": "Grace Garcia from TCS will speak at the conference in Hyderabad on Q3 2025 by 5 PM.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [18, 21, "ORG"], [54, 63, "GPE"], [67, 74, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773529+00:00", "text": "HCL Technologies partnered with another firm based in Lucknow on early 2026.", "entities": [[0, 16, "ORG"], [54, 61, "GPE"], [65, 75, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773532+00:00", "text": "According to Niket Tiwari, the office in Patna will be expanded.", "entities": [[13, 25, "PERSON"], [41, 46, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773536+00:00", "text": "The headquarters of ICICI Bank is located in Tokyo.", "entities": [[20, 30, "ORG"], [45, 50, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773541+00:00", "text": "Stanford University introduced ChatGPT on in 2022 at a price of $1.2 billion.", "entities": [[0, 19, "ORG"], [31, 38, "PRODUCT"], [42, 49, "DATE"], [64, 76, "MONEY"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773547+00:00", "text": "The majority of Americans in Jaipur speak Punjabi as their first language.", "entities": [[16, 25, "NORP"], [29, 35, "GPE"], [42, 49, "LANGUAGE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773551+00:00", "text": "According to Akash Jones, the office in Coimbatore will be expanded.", "entities": [[13, 24, "PERSON"], [40, 50, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773556+00:00", "text": "Pooja Verma from TCS will speak at the conference in Australia on next Friday around midnight.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [17, 20, "ORG"], [53, 62, "GPE"], [66, 77, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773560+00:00", "text": "Netflix announced on January 2023 that it will expand operations in United Kingdom.", "entities": [[0, 7, "ORG"], [21, 33, "DATE"], [68, 82, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773563+00:00", "text": "Priya Rao moved from China to pursue a career at Tesla.", "entities": [[0, 9, "PERSON"], [21, 26, "GPE"], [49, 54, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773567+00:00", "text": "Aditya Smith moved from Dubai to pursue a career at Zomato.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [24, 29, "GPE"], [52, 58, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773571+00:00", "text": "WHO raised ₹50 crore in its Series B round on next Friday.", "entities": [[0, 3, "ORG"], [11, 20, "MONEY"], [46, 57, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773575+00:00", "text": "Divya Sinha left TCS in Paris after five years.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [17, 20, "ORG"], [24, 29, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773578+00:00", "text": "Sanjay Martinez was born in Patna and studied at Zomato.", "entities": [[0, 15, "PERSON"], [28, 33, "GPE"], [49, 55, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773582+00:00", "text": "According to Olivia Joshi, the office in Japan will be expanded.", "entities": [[13, 25, "PERSON"], [41, 46, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773586+00:00", "text": "My name is Shruti Sinha and I work at Oxford University in Tokyo.", "entities": [[11, 23, "PERSON"], [38, 55, "ORG"], [59, 64, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773589+00:00", "text": "TCS announced on on 15 August that it will expand operations in Visakhapatnam.", "entities": [[0, 3, "ORG"], [17, 29, "DATE"], [64, 77, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773593+00:00", "text": "Reserve Bank of India announced on 3rd April 2024 that it will expand operations in Japan.", "entities": [[0, 21, "ORG"], [35, 49, "DATE"], [84, 89, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773596+00:00", "text": "Investors in San Francisco welcomed Meta's strategic announcement.", "entities": [[13, 26, "GPE"], [36, 40, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773599+00:00", "text": "Revenue grew by 12% to $1.2 billion in last Monday.", "entities": [[16, 19, "PERCENT"], [23, 35, "MONEY"], [39, 50, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773605+00:00", "text": "The majority of Republicans in Delhi speak French as their first language.", "entities": [[16, 27, "NORP"], [31, 36, "GPE"], [43, 49, "LANGUAGE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773608+00:00", "text": "The report by Emma Mehta from Uber shows impressive growth.", "entities": [[14, 24, "PERSON"], [30, 34, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773612+00:00", "text": "The deal worth 1 million dollars was signed in March 2025.", "entities": [[15, 32, "MONEY"], [47, 57, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773615+00:00", "text": "Rohit Reddy was born in Bangalore and studied at MIT.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [24, 33, "GPE"], [49, 52, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773619+00:00", "text": "The report by Sophia Sinha from Reliance Industries shows impressive growth.", "entities": [[14, 26, "PERSON"], [32, 51, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773624+00:00", "text": "Sneha Davis presented the product Surface Pro in the afternoon at ISRO in France.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [34, 45, "PRODUCT"], [66, 70, "ORG"], [74, 80, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773630+00:00", "text": "Priya Johnson authored Mahabharata, which sold over a 7% drop more copies in Coimbatore.", "entities": [[0, 13, "PERSON"], [23, 34, "WORK_OF_ART"], [52, 61, "PERCENT"], [77, 87, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773634+00:00", "text": "Swiggy announced on Q3 2025 that it will expand operations in San Francisco.", "entities": [[0, 6, "ORG"], [20, 27, "DATE"], [62, 75, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773637+00:00", "text": "United Nations plans to invest 1 million dollars in Kolkata by this year.", "entities": [[0, 14, "ORG"], [31, 48, "MONEY"], [63, 72, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773641+00:00", "text": "Noah Smith was born in India and studied at Netflix.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [23, 28, "GPE"], [44, 51, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773645+00:00", "text": "Nikhil Sharma moved from Australia to pursue a career at United Nations.", "entities": [[0, 13, "PERSON"], [25, 34, "GPE"], [57, 71, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773649+00:00", "text": "Revenue grew by more than 50% to ₹10 lakh in the 1990s.", "entities": [[16, 29, "PERCENT"], [33, 41, "MONEY"], [45, 54, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773652+00:00", "text": "Niket Iyer left Apple in Hyderabad after five years.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [16, 21, "ORG"], [25, 34, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773656+00:00", "text": "Microsoft partnered with another firm based in Surat on the 1990s.", "entities": [[0, 9, "ORG"], [47, 52, "GPE"], [56, 65, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773660+00:00", "text": "The report by Maria Kapoor from Meta shows impressive growth.", "entities": [[14, 26, "PERSON"], [32, 36, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773663+00:00", "text": "United Nations partnered with another firm based in Surat on two years ago.", "entities": [[0, 14, "ORG"], [52, 57, "GPE"], [61, 74, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773669+00:00", "text": "Alice Martinez presented the product OnePlus 12 by 5 PM at Swiggy in Canada.", "entities": [[0, 14, "PERSON"], [37, 47, "PRODUCT"], [59, 65, "ORG"], [69, 75, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773673+00:00", "text": "Sneha Agarwal left HCL Technologies in London after five years.", "entities": [[0, 13, "PERSON"], [19, 35, "ORG"], [39, 45, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773678+00:00", "text": "Raj Bose presented the product Pixel 8 at 10:30 AM at OpenAI in Vadodara.", "entities": [[0, 8, "PERSON"], [31, 38, "PRODUCT"], [54, 60, "ORG"], [64, 72, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773682+00:00", "text": "Divya Agarwal moved from Canada to pursue a career at Meta.", "entities": [[0, 13, "PERSON"], [25, 31, "GPE"], [54, 58, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773688+00:00", "text": "Bob Martinez authored Dune, which sold over 4.5% more copies in Kolkata.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [22, 26, "WORK_OF_ART"], [44, 48, "PERCENT"], [64, 71, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773695+00:00", "text": "Microsoft plans to invest ₹10 lakh in Patna by this year.", "entities": [[0, 9, "ORG"], [26, 34, "MONEY"], [47, 56, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773699+00:00", "text": "The headquarters of WHO is located in Kolkata.", "entities": [[20, 23, "ORG"], [38, 45, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773703+00:00", "text": "DRDO partnered with another firm based in Japan on March 2025.", "entities": [[0, 4, "ORG"], [42, 47, "GPE"], [51, 61, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773706+00:00", "text": "Revenue grew by over 30% to ₹2,000 in by December.", "entities": [[16, 24, "PERCENT"], [28, 34, "MONEY"], [38, 49, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773715+00:00", "text": "The headquarters of OpenAI is located in San Francisco.", "entities": [[20, 26, "ORG"], [41, 54, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773718+00:00", "text": "The report by Zoe Sinha from Byju's shows impressive growth.", "entities": [[14, 23, "PERSON"], [29, 35, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773724+00:00", "text": "Liam Bose presented the product Pixel 8 at 10:30 AM at DRDO in Visakhapatnam.", "entities": [[0, 9, "PERSON"], [32, 39, "PRODUCT"], [55, 59, "ORG"], [63, 76, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773727+00:00", "text": "World Bank reported a revenue increase of over 30% in 3rd April 2024.", "entities": [[0, 10, "ORG"], [42, 50, "PERCENT"], [54, 68, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773732+00:00", "text": "Microsoft plans to invest ₹2,000 in China by last Monday.", "entities": [[0, 9, "ORG"], [26, 32, "MONEY"], [45, 56, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773736+00:00", "text": "WHO plans to invest ₹50 crore in Berlin by by December.", "entities": [[0, 3, "ORG"], [20, 29, "MONEY"], [43, 54, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773739+00:00", "text": "Stanford University partnered with another firm based in Patna on March 2025.", "entities": [[0, 19, "ORG"], [57, 62, "GPE"], [66, 76, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773743+00:00", "text": "Grace Sinha moved from Chennai to pursue a career at Meta.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [23, 30, "GPE"], [53, 57, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773746+00:00", "text": "Investors in Indore welcomed MIT's strategic announcement.", "entities": [[13, 19, "GPE"], [29, 32, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773750+00:00", "text": "Bob Smith left Byju's in United States after five years.", "entities": [[0, 9, "PERSON"], [15, 21, "ORG"], [25, 38, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773754+00:00", "text": "Aditya Brown is the CEO of Swiggy.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [27, 33, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773757+00:00", "text": "Sundar Wilson was born in Ahmedabad and studied at MIT.", "entities": [[0, 13, "PERSON"], [26, 35, "GPE"], [51, 54, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773760+00:00", "text": "Tesla partnered with another firm based in Chennai on Q3 2025.", "entities": [[0, 5, "ORG"], [43, 50, "GPE"], [54, 61, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773766+00:00", "text": "IISc Bangalore introduced MacBook Pro on 3rd April 2024 at a price of ₹10 lakh.", "entities": [[0, 14, "ORG"], [26, 37, "PRODUCT"], [41, 55, "DATE"], [70, 78, "MONEY"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773769+00:00", "text": "Oxford University partnered with another firm based in Delhi on next Friday.", "entities": [[0, 17, "ORG"], [55, 60, "GPE"], [64, 75, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773773+00:00", "text": "HDFC Bank announced on in 2022 that it will expand operations in Sydney.", "entities": [[0, 9, "ORG"], [23, 30, "DATE"], [65, 71, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773776+00:00", "text": "Deepa Khan was born in Dubai and studied at Oxford University.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [23, 28, "GPE"], [44, 61, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773780+00:00", "text": "The headquarters of University of California is located in Jaipur.", "entities": [[20, 44, "ORG"], [59, 65, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773783+00:00", "text": "The deal worth ₹50 crore was signed in the 1990s.", "entities": [[15, 24, "MONEY"], [39, 48, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773790+00:00", "text": "Meta partnered with another firm based in Germany on this year.", "entities": [[0, 4, "ORG"], [42, 49, "GPE"], [53, 62, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773794+00:00", "text": "Infosys plans to invest ₹2,000 in Coimbatore by on 15 August.", "entities": [[0, 7, "ORG"], [24, 30, "MONEY"], [48, 60, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773798+00:00", "text": "Revenue grew by up by 15% to $500 million in the 1990s.", "entities": [[16, 25, "PERCENT"], [29, 41, "MONEY"], [45, 54, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773801+00:00", "text": "The headquarters of Amazon is located in Jaipur.", "entities": [[20, 26, "ORG"], [41, 47, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773805+00:00", "text": "TCS plans to invest ₹3.5 crore in San Francisco by 3rd April 2024.", "entities": [[0, 3, "ORG"], [20, 30, "MONEY"], [51, 65, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773811+00:00", "text": "Isha Johnson presented the product Google Maps at 10:30 AM at Byju's in Lucknow.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [35, 46, "PRODUCT"], [62, 68, "ORG"], [72, 79, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773815+00:00", "text": "IISc Bangalore announced on Q3 2025 that it will expand operations in Sydney.", "entities": [[0, 14, "ORG"], [28, 35, "DATE"], [70, 76, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773818+00:00", "text": "World Bank announced on January 2023 that it will expand operations in Berlin.", "entities": [[0, 10, "ORG"], [24, 36, "DATE"], [71, 77, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773822+00:00", "text": "DRDO reported a revenue increase of over 30% in 3rd April 2024.", "entities": [[0, 4, "ORG"], [36, 44, "PERCENT"], [48, 62, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773825+00:00", "text": "My name is Rohit Jain and I work at OpenAI in Nagpur.", "entities": [[11, 21, "PERSON"], [36, 42, "ORG"], [46, 52, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773829+00:00", "text": "TCS reported a revenue increase of a 7% drop in early 2026.", "entities": [[0, 3, "ORG"], [35, 44, "PERCENT"], [48, 58, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773832+00:00", "text": "Apple reported a revenue increase of more than 50% in this year.", "entities": [[0, 5, "ORG"], [37, 50, "PERCENT"], [54, 63, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773836+00:00", "text": "DRDO reported a revenue increase of more than 50% in in 2022.", "entities": [[0, 4, "ORG"], [36, 49, "PERCENT"], [53, 60, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773839+00:00", "text": "The headquarters of NASSCOM is located in United States.", "entities": [[20, 27, "ORG"], [42, 55, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773843+00:00", "text": "The headquarters of State Bank of India is located in Coimbatore.", "entities": [[20, 39, "ORG"], [54, 64, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773846+00:00", "text": "I am Tanya Lee and I live in Visakhapatnam.", "entities": [[5, 14, "PERSON"], [29, 42, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773850+00:00", "text": "Stanford University plans to invest ₹10 lakh in London by this year.", "entities": [[0, 19, "ORG"], [36, 44, "MONEY"], [58, 67, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773854+00:00", "text": "Olivia Tiwari left Reserve Bank of India in Tokyo after five years.", "entities": [[0, 13, "PERSON"], [19, 40, "ORG"], [44, 49, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773861+00:00", "text": "The majority of Sikhs in United States speak Kannada as their first language.", "entities": [[16, 21, "NORP"], [25, 38, "GPE"], [45, 52, "LANGUAGE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773865+00:00", "text": "NASSCOM plans to invest €200 billion in Indore by this year.", "entities": [[0, 7, "ORG"], [24, 36, "MONEY"], [50, 59, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773868+00:00", "text": "I am Sundar Taylor and I live in Sydney.", "entities": [[5, 18, "PERSON"], [33, 39, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773872+00:00", "text": "I am Rohit Kapoor and I live in Bhopal.", "entities": [[5, 17, "PERSON"], [32, 38, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773875+00:00", "text": "According to Olivia Sinha, the office in China will be expanded.", "entities": [[13, 25, "PERSON"], [41, 46, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773879+00:00", "text": "Rohit Sharma moved from Mumbai to pursue a career at Infosys.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [24, 30, "GPE"], [53, 60, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773883+00:00", "text": "The headquarters of Stanford University is located in Nagpur.", "entities": [[20, 39, "ORG"], [54, 60, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773886+00:00", "text": "I am Alice Joshi and I live in Kolkata.", "entities": [[5, 16, "PERSON"], [31, 38, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773890+00:00", "text": "HCL Technologies announced on 3rd April 2024 that it will expand operations in Japan.", "entities": [[0, 16, "ORG"], [30, 44, "DATE"], [79, 84, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773897+00:00", "text": "The majority of Americans in London speak Kannada as their first language.", "entities": [[16, 25, "NORP"], [29, 35, "GPE"], [42, 49, "LANGUAGE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773901+00:00", "text": "According to Noah Kumar, the office in San Francisco will be expanded.", "entities": [[13, 23, "PERSON"], [39, 52, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773906+00:00", "text": "The majority of Democrats in New York speak Marathi as their first language.", "entities": [[16, 25, "NORP"], [29, 37, "GPE"], [44, 51, "LANGUAGE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773910+00:00", "text": "Revenue grew by up by 15% to $500 million in 3rd April 2024.", "entities": [[16, 25, "PERCENT"], [29, 41, "MONEY"], [45, 59, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773914+00:00", "text": "Netflix raised 50 million euros in its Series B round on two years ago.", "entities": [[0, 7, "ORG"], [15, 31, "MONEY"], [57, 70, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773917+00:00", "text": "The report by Kunal Brown from Infosys shows impressive growth.", "entities": [[14, 25, "PERSON"], [31, 38, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773922+00:00", "text": "Olivia Singh from Google will speak at the conference in Vadodara on on 15 August around midnight.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [18, 24, "ORG"], [57, 65, "GPE"], [69, 81, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773926+00:00", "text": "My name is Liam Thomas and I work at Swiggy in Patna.", "entities": [[11, 22, "PERSON"], [37, 43, "ORG"], [47, 52, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773930+00:00", "text": "Wipro plans to invest 50 million euros in Singapore by two years ago.", "entities": [[0, 5, "ORG"], [22, 38, "MONEY"], [55, 68, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773934+00:00", "text": "The deal worth $500 million was signed in January 2023.", "entities": [[15, 27, "MONEY"], [42, 54, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773937+00:00", "text": "Investors in United Kingdom welcomed United Nations's strategic announcement.", "entities": [[13, 27, "GPE"], [37, 51, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773942+00:00", "text": "Karan Mehta presented the product OnePlus 12 around midnight at NASSCOM in Indore.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [34, 44, "PRODUCT"], [64, 71, "ORG"], [75, 81, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773946+00:00", "text": "I am Sundar Rao and I live in New York.", "entities": [[5, 15, "PERSON"], [30, 38, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773949+00:00", "text": "Wipro partnered with another firm based in India on this year.", "entities": [[0, 5, "ORG"], [43, 48, "GPE"], [52, 61, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773953+00:00", "text": "According to Arjun Singh, the office in Sydney will be expanded.", "entities": [[13, 24, "PERSON"], [40, 46, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773956+00:00", "text": "My name is Vinay Kumar and I work at ISRO in Canada.", "entities": [[11, 22, "PERSON"], [37, 41, "ORG"], [45, 51, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773959+00:00", "text": "Investors in Berlin welcomed MIT's strategic announcement.", "entities": [[13, 19, "GPE"], [29, 32, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773963+00:00", "text": "Microsoft announced on Q3 2025 that it will expand operations in France.", "entities": [[0, 9, "ORG"], [23, 30, "DATE"], [65, 71, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773967+00:00", "text": "Amazon raised 50 million euros in its Series B round on in 2022.", "entities": [[0, 6, "ORG"], [14, 30, "MONEY"], [56, 63, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773971+00:00", "text": "The headquarters of Meta is located in Dubai.", "entities": [[20, 24, "ORG"], [39, 44, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773974+00:00", "text": "IISc Bangalore partnered with another firm based in United Kingdom on on 15 August.", "entities": [[0, 14, "ORG"], [52, 66, "GPE"], [70, 82, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773980+00:00", "text": "Aarav Davis authored Mahabharata, which sold over 4.5% more copies in Germany.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [21, 32, "WORK_OF_ART"], [50, 54, "PERCENT"], [70, 77, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773984+00:00", "text": "Revenue grew by 12% to €200 billion in by December.", "entities": [[16, 19, "PERCENT"], [23, 35, "MONEY"], [39, 50, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773987+00:00", "text": "State Bank of India reported a revenue increase of nearly 80% in in 2022.", "entities": [[0, 19, "ORG"], [51, 61, "PERCENT"], [65, 72, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773991+00:00", "text": "Meera Lee left OpenAI in Bangalore after five years.", "entities": [[0, 9, "PERSON"], [15, 21, "ORG"], [25, 34, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773994+00:00", "text": "State Bank of India announced on next Friday that it will expand operations in Indore.", "entities": [[0, 19, "ORG"], [33, 44, "DATE"], [79, 85, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.773998+00:00", "text": "United Nations announced on January 2023 that it will expand operations in Chennai.", "entities": [[0, 14, "ORG"], [28, 40, "DATE"], [75, 82, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774001+00:00", "text": "NASSCOM announced on March 2025 that it will expand operations in Indore.", "entities": [[0, 7, "ORG"], [21, 31, "DATE"], [66, 72, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774005+00:00", "text": "The report by Tanya Gupta from Zomato shows impressive growth.", "entities": [[14, 25, "PERSON"], [31, 37, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774008+00:00", "text": "Investors in Kochi welcomed State Bank of India's strategic announcement.", "entities": [[13, 18, "GPE"], [28, 47, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774012+00:00", "text": "My name is Emma Trivedi and I work at Paytm in Coimbatore.", "entities": [[11, 23, "PERSON"], [38, 43, "ORG"], [47, 57, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774017+00:00", "text": "University of California announced on by December that it will expand operations in Paris.", "entities": [[0, 24, "ORG"], [38, 49, "DATE"], [84, 89, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774022+00:00", "text": "IIT Delhi introduced ChatGPT on in 2022 at a price of 50 million euros.", "entities": [[0, 9, "ORG"], [21, 28, "PRODUCT"], [32, 39, "DATE"], [54, 70, "MONEY"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774026+00:00", "text": "Ananya Martin moved from Kochi to pursue a career at ICICI Bank.", "entities": [[0, 13, "PERSON"], [25, 30, "GPE"], [53, 63, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774029+00:00", "text": "The deal worth ₹3.5 crore was signed in this year.", "entities": [[15, 25, "MONEY"], [40, 49, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774033+00:00", "text": "HDFC Bank announced on two years ago that it will expand operations in China.", "entities": [[0, 9, "ORG"], [23, 36, "DATE"], [71, 76, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774038+00:00", "text": "Alice Davis presented the product Google Maps around midnight at Swiggy in Kolkata.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [34, 45, "PRODUCT"], [65, 71, "ORG"], [75, 82, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774042+00:00", "text": "I am Srishti Trivedi and I live in Paris.", "entities": [[5, 20, "PERSON"], [35, 40, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774045+00:00", "text": "Paytm reported a revenue increase of up by 15% in January 2023.", "entities": [[0, 5, "ORG"], [37, 46, "PERCENT"], [50, 62, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774059+00:00", "text": "OpenAI introduced OnePlus 12 on January 2023 at a price of 50 million euros.", "entities": [[0, 6, "ORG"], [18, 28, "PRODUCT"], [32, 44, "DATE"], [59, 75, "MONEY"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774063+00:00", "text": "Investors in Vadodara welcomed Paytm's strategic announcement.", "entities": [[13, 21, "GPE"], [31, 36, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774069+00:00", "text": "Liam Trivedi from MIT will speak at the conference in Pune on March 2025 in the afternoon.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [18, 21, "ORG"], [54, 58, "GPE"], [62, 72, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774074+00:00", "text": "Kunal Agarwal from TCS will speak at the conference in Delhi on Q3 2025 at dawn.", "entities": [[0, 13, "PERSON"], [19, 22, "ORG"], [55, 60, "GPE"], [64, 71, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774078+00:00", "text": "Revenue grew by up by 15% to $1.2 billion in early 2026.", "entities": [[16, 25, "PERCENT"], [29, 41, "MONEY"], [45, 55, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774081+00:00", "text": "Investors in Jaipur welcomed Wipro's strategic announcement.", "entities": [[13, 19, "GPE"], [29, 34, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774085+00:00", "text": "DRDO announced on next Friday that it will expand operations in Bangalore.", "entities": [[0, 4, "ORG"], [18, 29, "DATE"], [64, 73, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774089+00:00", "text": "The deal worth ₹2,000 was signed in early 2026.", "entities": [[15, 21, "MONEY"], [36, 46, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774092+00:00", "text": "The report by Deepa Rao from ISRO shows impressive growth.", "entities": [[14, 23, "PERSON"], [29, 33, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774096+00:00", "text": "According to Maria Nair, the office in Dubai will be expanded.", "entities": [[13, 23, "PERSON"], [39, 44, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774099+00:00", "text": "Ananya Martin left NASSCOM in Paris after five years.", "entities": [[0, 13, "PERSON"], [19, 26, "ORG"], [30, 35, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774103+00:00", "text": "Divya Iyer was born in Coimbatore and studied at DRDO.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [23, 33, "GPE"], [49, 53, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774107+00:00", "text": "Vikram Taylor is the CEO of University of California.", "entities": [[0, 13, "PERSON"], [28, 52, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774112+00:00", "text": "Manish Sinha presented the product OnePlus 12 around midnight at DRDO in Surat.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [35, 45, "PRODUCT"], [65, 69, "ORG"], [73, 78, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774117+00:00", "text": "MIT reported a revenue increase of a 7% drop in January 2023.", "entities": [[0, 3, "ORG"], [35, 44, "PERCENT"], [48, 60, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774121+00:00", "text": "Ananya Sharma is the CEO of Netflix.", "entities": [[0, 13, "PERSON"], [28, 35, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774124+00:00", "text": "Securities Exchange Board of India announced on last Monday that it will expand operations in Dubai.", "entities": [[0, 34, "ORG"], [48, 59, "DATE"], [94, 99, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774128+00:00", "text": "University of California raised ₹10 lakh in its Series B round on the 1990s.", "entities": [[0, 24, "ORG"], [32, 40, "MONEY"], [66, 75, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774134+00:00", "text": "Amit Wilson presented the product Pixel 8 in the afternoon at Amazon in Bhopal.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [34, 41, "PRODUCT"], [62, 68, "ORG"], [72, 78, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774137+00:00", "text": "I am Karan Bansal and I live in Delhi.", "entities": [[5, 17, "PERSON"], [32, 37, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774141+00:00", "text": "Investors in Kochi welcomed Meta's strategic announcement.", "entities": [[13, 18, "GPE"], [28, 32, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774145+00:00", "text": "The report by Rohit Dubey from IIT Delhi shows impressive growth.", "entities": [[14, 25, "PERSON"], [31, 40, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774148+00:00", "text": "The headquarters of Netflix is located in New York.", "entities": [[20, 27, "ORG"], [42, 50, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774152+00:00", "text": "Gaurav Trivedi is the CEO of University of California.", "entities": [[0, 14, "PERSON"], [29, 53, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774156+00:00", "text": "The report by Sundar Mishra from WHO shows impressive growth.", "entities": [[14, 27, "PERSON"], [33, 36, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774159+00:00", "text": "According to Vikram Sinha, the office in Canada will be expanded.", "entities": [[13, 25, "PERSON"], [41, 47, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774163+00:00", "text": "Sanjay Joshi left Securities Exchange Board of India in Germany after five years.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [18, 52, "ORG"], [56, 63, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774166+00:00", "text": "Raj Verma is the CEO of World Bank.", "entities": [[0, 9, "PERSON"], [24, 34, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774170+00:00", "text": "The deal worth ₹2,000 was signed in Q3 2025.", "entities": [[15, 21, "MONEY"], [36, 43, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774173+00:00", "text": "IIT Delhi announced on in 2022 that it will expand operations in India.", "entities": [[0, 9, "ORG"], [23, 30, "DATE"], [65, 70, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774177+00:00", "text": "The report by Shruti Jain from Paytm shows impressive growth.", "entities": [[14, 25, "PERSON"], [31, 36, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774180+00:00", "text": "Revenue grew by over 30% to 1 million dollars in on 15 August.", "entities": [[16, 24, "PERCENT"], [28, 45, "MONEY"], [49, 61, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774184+00:00", "text": "The headquarters of Tesla is located in Delhi.", "entities": [[20, 25, "ORG"], [40, 45, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774187+00:00", "text": "IIT Delhi partnered with another firm based in Mumbai on Q3 2025.", "entities": [[0, 9, "ORG"], [47, 53, "GPE"], [57, 64, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774191+00:00", "text": "Investors in Patna welcomed Securities Exchange Board of India's strategic announcement.", "entities": [[13, 18, "GPE"], [28, 62, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774194+00:00", "text": "Ananya Sinha moved from Lucknow to pursue a career at IIT Delhi.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [24, 31, "GPE"], [54, 63, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774197+00:00", "text": "Ravi Bose moved from London to pursue a career at Flipkart.", "entities": [[0, 9, "PERSON"], [21, 27, "GPE"], [50, 58, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774201+00:00", "text": "Olivia Martinez left University of California in Coimbatore after five years.", "entities": [[0, 15, "PERSON"], [21, 45, "ORG"], [49, 59, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774204+00:00", "text": "Noah Jones was born in United Kingdom and studied at Meta.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [23, 37, "GPE"], [53, 57, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774210+00:00", "text": "Oxford University introduced ChatGPT on by December at a price of 1 million dollars.", "entities": [[0, 17, "ORG"], [29, 36, "PRODUCT"], [40, 51, "DATE"], [66, 83, "MONEY"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774214+00:00", "text": "The deal worth 50 million euros was signed in two years ago.", "entities": [[15, 31, "MONEY"], [46, 59, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774217+00:00", "text": "According to Charlie Bansal, the office in Nagpur will be expanded.", "entities": [[13, 27, "PERSON"], [43, 49, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774220+00:00", "text": "Ananya Wilson was born in India and studied at IIT Bombay.", "entities": [[0, 13, "PERSON"], [26, 31, "GPE"], [47, 57, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774228+00:00", "text": "Investors in Tokyo welcomed World Bank's strategic announcement.", "entities": [[13, 18, "GPE"], [28, 38, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774232+00:00", "text": "According to Ethan Bose, the office in Indore will be expanded.", "entities": [[13, 23, "PERSON"], [39, 45, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774236+00:00", "text": "Oxford University plans to invest 1 million dollars in Hyderabad by two years ago.", "entities": [[0, 17, "ORG"], [34, 51, "MONEY"], [68, 81, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774239+00:00", "text": "Sundar Joshi left TCS in Australia after five years.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [18, 21, "ORG"], [25, 34, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774243+00:00", "text": "Ankit Bose left United Nations in Dubai after five years.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [16, 30, "ORG"], [34, 39, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774246+00:00", "text": "The headquarters of NASSCOM is located in Bangalore.", "entities": [[20, 27, "ORG"], [42, 51, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774250+00:00", "text": "Tesla plans to invest $500 million in Tokyo by two years ago.", "entities": [[0, 5, "ORG"], [22, 34, "MONEY"], [47, 60, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774255+00:00", "text": "Manish Taylor left WHO in Bangalore after five years.", "entities": [[0, 13, "PERSON"], [19, 22, "ORG"], [26, 35, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774260+00:00", "text": "Ravi Thomas from Ola will speak at the conference in Australia on next Friday at 9 AM.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [17, 20, "ORG"], [53, 62, "GPE"], [66, 77, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774264+00:00", "text": "The deal worth 50 million euros was signed in by December.", "entities": [[15, 31, "MONEY"], [46, 57, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774268+00:00", "text": "Vikram Patel is the CEO of Microsoft.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [27, 36, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774272+00:00", "text": "Ankit Miller moved from Ahmedabad to pursue a career at Netflix.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [24, 33, "GPE"], [56, 63, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774275+00:00", "text": "I am Emma Patel and I live in Singapore.", "entities": [[5, 15, "PERSON"], [30, 39, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774278+00:00", "text": "Stanford University partnered with another firm based in Pune on by December.", "entities": [[0, 19, "ORG"], [57, 61, "GPE"], [65, 76, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774282+00:00", "text": "Neha Sinha is the CEO of Paytm.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [25, 30, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774285+00:00", "text": "Kavya Reddy moved from Pune to pursue a career at Ola.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [23, 27, "GPE"], [50, 53, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774291+00:00", "text": "James Rao authored Mahabharata, which sold over a 7% drop more copies in San Francisco.", "entities": [[0, 9, "PERSON"], [19, 30, "WORK_OF_ART"], [48, 57, "PERCENT"], [73, 86, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774295+00:00", "text": "My name is Vikas Verma and I work at University of California in France.", "entities": [[11, 22, "PERSON"], [37, 61, "ORG"], [65, 71, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774298+00:00", "text": "World Bank raised 50 million euros in its Series B round on on 15 August.", "entities": [[0, 10, "ORG"], [18, 34, "MONEY"], [60, 72, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774302+00:00", "text": "The deal worth ₹2,000 was signed in March 2025.", "entities": [[15, 21, "MONEY"], [36, 46, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774305+00:00", "text": "MIT partnered with another firm based in Ahmedabad on Q3 2025.", "entities": [[0, 3, "ORG"], [41, 50, "GPE"], [54, 61, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774309+00:00", "text": "United Nations partnered with another firm based in Germany on the 1990s.", "entities": [[0, 14, "ORG"], [52, 59, "GPE"], [63, 72, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774312+00:00", "text": "Uber reported a revenue increase of up by 15% in the 1990s.", "entities": [[0, 4, "ORG"], [36, 45, "PERCENT"], [49, 58, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774316+00:00", "text": "The deal worth ₹10 lakh was signed in next Friday.", "entities": [[15, 23, "MONEY"], [38, 49, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774319+00:00", "text": "Kunal Jones moved from United Kingdom to pursue a career at HCL Technologies.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [23, 37, "GPE"], [60, 76, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774322+00:00", "text": "United Nations partnered with another firm based in Jaipur on the 1990s.", "entities": [[0, 14, "ORG"], [52, 58, "GPE"], [62, 71, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774326+00:00", "text": "NASSCOM reported a revenue increase of more than 50% in this year.", "entities": [[0, 7, "ORG"], [39, 52, "PERCENT"], [56, 65, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774329+00:00", "text": "Investors in India welcomed HCL Technologies's strategic announcement.", "entities": [[13, 18, "GPE"], [28, 44, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774333+00:00", "text": "According to Srishti Jain, the office in Mumbai will be expanded.", "entities": [[13, 25, "PERSON"], [41, 47, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774336+00:00", "text": "According to Rahul Yadav, the office in Paris will be expanded.", "entities": [[13, 24, "PERSON"], [40, 45, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774339+00:00", "text": "IISc Bangalore reported a revenue increase of more than 50% in by December.", "entities": [[0, 14, "ORG"], [46, 59, "PERCENT"], [63, 74, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774343+00:00", "text": "Akash Yadav was born in Bhopal and studied at Microsoft.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [24, 30, "GPE"], [46, 55, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774347+00:00", "text": "Niket Wilson was born in Tokyo and studied at ICICI Bank.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [25, 30, "GPE"], [46, 56, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774352+00:00", "text": "According to Alice Joshi, the office in Berlin will be expanded.", "entities": [[13, 24, "PERSON"], [40, 46, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774355+00:00", "text": "Investors in Ahmedabad welcomed Reserve Bank of India's strategic announcement.", "entities": [[13, 22, "GPE"], [32, 53, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774359+00:00", "text": "Revenue grew by 12% to ₹3.5 crore in January 2023.", "entities": [[16, 19, "PERCENT"], [23, 33, "MONEY"], [37, 49, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774363+00:00", "text": "My name is Sophia Sharma and I work at State Bank of India in Kochi.", "entities": [[11, 24, "PERSON"], [39, 58, "ORG"], [62, 67, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774366+00:00", "text": "Netflix reported a revenue increase of up by 15% in next Friday.", "entities": [[0, 7, "ORG"], [39, 48, "PERCENT"], [52, 63, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774370+00:00", "text": "Grace Jain left World Bank in United States after five years.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [16, 26, "ORG"], [30, 43, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774373+00:00", "text": "I am Rahul Kumar and I live in Indore.", "entities": [[5, 16, "PERSON"], [31, 37, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774377+00:00", "text": "The deal worth €200 billion was signed in the 1990s.", "entities": [[15, 27, "MONEY"], [42, 51, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774381+00:00", "text": "Yash Martin was born in Visakhapatnam and studied at Zomato.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [24, 37, "GPE"], [53, 59, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774387+00:00", "text": "Bob Patel authored Inception, which sold over just 2% more copies in Pune.", "entities": [[0, 9, "PERSON"], [19, 28, "WORK_OF_ART"], [46, 53, "PERCENT"], [69, 73, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774391+00:00", "text": "Oxford University plans to invest 1 million dollars in Patna by the 1990s.", "entities": [[0, 17, "ORG"], [34, 51, "MONEY"], [64, 73, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774395+00:00", "text": "Harvard University announced on two years ago that it will expand operations in Hyderabad.", "entities": [[0, 18, "ORG"], [32, 45, "DATE"], [80, 89, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774398+00:00", "text": "The headquarters of Swiggy is located in Singapore.", "entities": [[20, 26, "ORG"], [41, 50, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774402+00:00", "text": "Investors in United States welcomed MIT's strategic announcement.", "entities": [[13, 26, "GPE"], [36, 39, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774405+00:00", "text": "The headquarters of HDFC Bank is located in London.", "entities": [[20, 29, "ORG"], [44, 50, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774409+00:00", "text": "Reserve Bank of India plans to invest $1.2 billion in China by March 2025.", "entities": [[0, 21, "ORG"], [38, 50, "MONEY"], [63, 73, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774414+00:00", "text": "Karan Trivedi presented the product MacBook Pro in the afternoon at Apple in Bangalore.", "entities": [[0, 13, "PERSON"], [36, 47, "PRODUCT"], [68, 73, "ORG"], [77, 86, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774420+00:00", "text": "The majority of Democrats in Nagpur speak Japanese as their first language.", "entities": [[16, 25, "NORP"], [29, 35, "GPE"], [42, 50, "LANGUAGE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774424+00:00", "text": "My name is Yash Jones and I work at Swiggy in Lucknow.", "entities": [[11, 21, "PERSON"], [36, 42, "ORG"], [46, 53, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774427+00:00", "text": "ICICI Bank announced on two years ago that it will expand operations in Australia.", "entities": [[0, 10, "ORG"], [24, 37, "DATE"], [72, 81, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774431+00:00", "text": "The deal worth ₹2,000 was signed in 3rd April 2024.", "entities": [[15, 21, "MONEY"], [36, 50, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774434+00:00", "text": "The headquarters of Google is located in Mumbai.", "entities": [[20, 26, "ORG"], [41, 47, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774437+00:00", "text": "Revenue grew by over 30% to ₹2,000 in January 2023.", "entities": [[16, 24, "PERCENT"], [28, 34, "MONEY"], [38, 50, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774442+00:00", "text": "The report by Ravi Trivedi from Tesla shows impressive growth.", "entities": [[14, 26, "PERSON"], [32, 37, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774446+00:00", "text": "Infosys reported a revenue increase of just 2% in March 2025.", "entities": [[0, 7, "ORG"], [39, 46, "PERCENT"], [50, 60, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774449+00:00", "text": "Meta announced on the 1990s that it will expand operations in San Francisco.", "entities": [[0, 4, "ORG"], [18, 27, "DATE"], [62, 75, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774452+00:00", "text": "Harvard University reported a revenue increase of over 30% in early 2026.", "entities": [[0, 18, "ORG"], [50, 58, "PERCENT"], [62, 72, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774456+00:00", "text": "IISc Bangalore announced on January 2023 that it will expand operations in Canada.", "entities": [[0, 14, "ORG"], [28, 40, "DATE"], [75, 81, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774461+00:00", "text": "Niket Jones presented the product MacBook Pro at dawn at Infosys in Ahmedabad.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [34, 45, "PRODUCT"], [57, 64, "ORG"], [68, 77, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774465+00:00", "text": "My name is Vikram Nair and I work at United Nations in Visakhapatnam.", "entities": [[11, 22, "PERSON"], [37, 51, "ORG"], [55, 68, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774469+00:00", "text": "Revenue grew by nearly 80% to ₹3.5 crore in January 2023.", "entities": [[16, 26, "PERCENT"], [30, 40, "MONEY"], [44, 56, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774472+00:00", "text": "According to David Yadav, the office in Patna will be expanded.", "entities": [[13, 24, "PERSON"], [40, 45, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774476+00:00", "text": "Oxford University announced on this year that it will expand operations in Hyderabad.", "entities": [[0, 17, "ORG"], [31, 40, "DATE"], [75, 84, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774482+00:00", "text": "James Bansal from Byju's will speak at the conference in Jaipur on on 15 August at dawn.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [18, 24, "ORG"], [57, 63, "GPE"], [67, 79, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774485+00:00", "text": "My name is Niket Mehta and I work at Tata Consultancy Services in Indore.", "entities": [[11, 22, "PERSON"], [37, 62, "ORG"], [66, 72, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774491+00:00", "text": "Deepa Taylor authored Pathaan, which sold over a 7% drop more copies in New York.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [22, 29, "WORK_OF_ART"], [47, 56, "PERCENT"], [72, 80, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774497+00:00", "text": "I am Sneha Garcia and I live in Kolkata.", "entities": [[5, 17, "PERSON"], [32, 39, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774503+00:00", "text": "Vikram Miller authored 2001: A Space Odyssey, which sold over just 2% more copies in Tokyo.", "entities": [[0, 13, "PERSON"], [23, 44, "WORK_OF_ART"], [62, 69, "PERCENT"], [85, 90, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774506+00:00", "text": "According to Raj Sinha, the office in Ahmedabad will be expanded.", "entities": [[13, 22, "PERSON"], [38, 47, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774510+00:00", "text": "Paytm announced on next Friday that it will expand operations in Kanpur.", "entities": [[0, 5, "ORG"], [19, 30, "DATE"], [65, 71, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774514+00:00", "text": "Oxford University plans to invest ₹10 lakh in Mumbai by this year.", "entities": [[0, 17, "ORG"], [34, 42, "MONEY"], [56, 65, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774517+00:00", "text": "Isha Jones is the CEO of Infosys.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [25, 32, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774521+00:00", "text": "University of California raised €200 billion in its Series B round on this year.", "entities": [[0, 24, "ORG"], [32, 44, "MONEY"], [70, 79, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774525+00:00", "text": "According to Sneha Patel, the office in Hyderabad will be expanded.", "entities": [[13, 24, "PERSON"], [40, 49, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774528+00:00", "text": "Apple reported a revenue increase of up by 15% in the 1990s.", "entities": [[0, 5, "ORG"], [37, 46, "PERCENT"], [50, 59, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774531+00:00", "text": "Tesla announced on two years ago that it will expand operations in Berlin.", "entities": [[0, 5, "ORG"], [19, 32, "DATE"], [67, 73, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774535+00:00", "text": "My name is William Smith and I work at ISRO in Mumbai.", "entities": [[11, 24, "PERSON"], [39, 43, "ORG"], [47, 53, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774540+00:00", "text": "Google introduced MacBook Pro on last Monday at a price of ₹10 lakh.", "entities": [[0, 6, "ORG"], [18, 29, "PRODUCT"], [33, 44, "DATE"], [59, 67, "MONEY"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774544+00:00", "text": "The report by Grace Tiwari from State Bank of India shows impressive growth.", "entities": [[14, 26, "PERSON"], [32, 51, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774547+00:00", "text": "The report by Alice Martin from Meta shows impressive growth.", "entities": [[14, 26, "PERSON"], [32, 36, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774551+00:00", "text": "I am Bob Tiwari and I live in Kanpur.", "entities": [[5, 15, "PERSON"], [30, 36, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774555+00:00", "text": "Meta plans to invest $1.2 billion in Bangalore by Q3 2025.", "entities": [[0, 4, "ORG"], [21, 33, "MONEY"], [50, 57, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774558+00:00", "text": "My name is David Sharma and I work at Securities Exchange Board of India in Singapore.", "entities": [[11, 23, "PERSON"], [38, 72, "ORG"], [76, 85, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774563+00:00", "text": "Investors in Kochi welcomed Reserve Bank of India's strategic announcement.", "entities": [[13, 18, "GPE"], [28, 49, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774566+00:00", "text": "According to Rahul Sharma, the office in Sydney will be expanded.", "entities": [[13, 25, "PERSON"], [41, 47, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774572+00:00", "text": "The majority of Buddhists in Tokyo speak Bengali as their first language.", "entities": [[16, 25, "NORP"], [29, 34, "GPE"], [41, 48, "LANGUAGE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774576+00:00", "text": "Ola partnered with another firm based in Mumbai on March 2025.", "entities": [[0, 3, "ORG"], [41, 47, "GPE"], [51, 61, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774579+00:00", "text": "Revenue grew by 4.5% to ₹3.5 crore in January 2023.", "entities": [[16, 20, "PERCENT"], [24, 34, "MONEY"], [38, 50, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774583+00:00", "text": "TCS announced on next Friday that it will expand operations in Coimbatore.", "entities": [[0, 3, "ORG"], [17, 28, "DATE"], [63, 73, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774588+00:00", "text": "DRDO introduced Galaxy S24 on early 2026 at a price of $1.2 billion.", "entities": [[0, 4, "ORG"], [16, 26, "PRODUCT"], [30, 40, "DATE"], [55, 67, "MONEY"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774592+00:00", "text": "Bob Martinez left Reserve Bank of India in Chennai after five years.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [18, 39, "ORG"], [43, 50, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774596+00:00", "text": "Revenue grew by nearly 80% to €200 billion in in 2022.", "entities": [[16, 26, "PERCENT"], [30, 42, "MONEY"], [46, 53, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774600+00:00", "text": "Harvard University raised €200 billion in its Series B round on January 2023.", "entities": [[0, 18, "ORG"], [26, 38, "MONEY"], [64, 76, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774605+00:00", "text": "Srishti Iyer presented the product Gemini at noon at Infosys in Sydney.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [35, 41, "PRODUCT"], [53, 60, "ORG"], [64, 70, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774608+00:00", "text": "The headquarters of Harvard University is located in Kochi.", "entities": [[20, 38, "ORG"], [53, 58, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774614+00:00", "text": "Ankit Tiwari authored Inception, which sold over nearly 80% more copies in Lucknow.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [22, 31, "WORK_OF_ART"], [49, 59, "PERCENT"], [75, 82, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774620+00:00", "text": "Yash Davis from IIT Bombay will speak at the conference in New York on last Monday at 10:30 AM.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [16, 26, "ORG"], [59, 67, "GPE"], [71, 82, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774624+00:00", "text": "Akash Miller moved from Pune to pursue a career at MIT.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [24, 28, "GPE"], [51, 54, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774627+00:00", "text": "Grace Thomas moved from Bhopal to pursue a career at Apple.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [24, 30, "GPE"], [53, 58, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774631+00:00", "text": "Alice Nair is the CEO of IIT Bombay.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [25, 35, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774634+00:00", "text": "Meta reported a revenue increase of just 2% in next Friday.", "entities": [[0, 4, "ORG"], [36, 43, "PERCENT"], [47, 58, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774641+00:00", "text": "Harvard University introduced iPhone 15 on next Friday at a price of ₹2,000.", "entities": [[0, 18, "ORG"], [30, 39, "PRODUCT"], [43, 54, "DATE"], [69, 75, "MONEY"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774645+00:00", "text": "Revenue grew by more than 50% to 50 million euros in two years ago.", "entities": [[16, 29, "PERCENT"], [33, 49, "MONEY"], [53, 66, "DATE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774649+00:00", "text": "Bob Jain was born in Kanpur and studied at HDFC Bank.", "entities": [[0, 8, "PERSON"], [21, 27, "GPE"], [43, 52, "ORG"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774653+00:00", "text": "I am Akash Patel and I live in Bangalore.", "entities": [[5, 16, "PERSON"], [31, 40, "GPE"]]}
{"created_at": "2026-04-21T02:09:10.774656+00:00", "text": "IISc Bangalore announced on by December that it will expand operations in Paris.", "entities": [[0, 14, "ORG"], [28, 39, "DATE"], [74, 79, "GPE"]]}
